New Classic Retro Synthwave
Thank you for purchase!

Best Electronic Music For Your Arcade Games.

Electronic and emotional, synthesized, retro wave.
This perfectly fits for new retro arcade games, shootings, racing, action.
 
In this package you'll find 5 instrumental tracks and 1 vocal track.
All of the wav tracks are available as high quality 16 bit, and high quality re-mastered for using in games.
And, this pack includes ogg seamless loop and 3 separated loop wav files for each music track.

------------------

Content

01. RETRO METAPHOR
02. REVIVE LUVS feat. Norico
03. DESCENDING AIR CURRENT
04. ARPCHAIN
05. DETROIT BEAT
06. REVIVE LUVS(no vocal)


------------------

All tracks are produced by ISAo
SOUND AIRYLUVS

http://airyluvs.com
isao@airyluvs.com

*If you want to order new music or arrangement, please contact to me :)

Thanks.
01/16/2020
